# https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&category=12&difficulty=easy&type=boolean
question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album &#039;Flood&#039; in 1990. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "John Williams composed the music for &quot;Star Wars&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
